(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
YouTubeチラ見せ枠
YouTube Sneak Peek
聖なる夜
A holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin' let's leap over
Highになって Highになるまで ダンスしてたいな
Until we get high, let's keep dancing
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin' even beyond the ocean
もっと もっと 近づきたいな
I want to get closer and closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
Woah oh oh oh Woah oh oh oh
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can be together
Gimme gimme step Gimme gimme hop
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
Woah oh oh oh Woah oh oh oh
何度も もっと高く飛びたいな
Again and again, I want to jump even higher
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。
Right here.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close you could almost touch.
2025.12.21 Sun
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you can meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ！
Here we go!
Hyper Jumpin'　飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's jump across!
ハイになって　ハイになるまで　足していきな
Get high, keep adding to it until we're high
Hyper Jumpin'　海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin'! All the way across the sea
もっと　もっと　近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live show where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
From 360 degrees, from everywhere.
もっと　もっと　高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
I'm right here. So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ！
Here we go!
Hyper Jumpin'　飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's jump across!
ハイになって　ハイになるまで　足していきな
Get high, keep adding to it until we're high
Hyper Jumpin'　海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin'! All the way across the sea
もっと　もっと　近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live show where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
From 360 degrees, from everywhere.
もっと　もっと　高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
I'm right here. So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap over
ハイになれ ハイになるまで 出していきな
Get high, until you're high, let it all out
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sea
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
みるだけじゃない
More than just watching
Woah-oh-oh-oh, Woah-oh-oh-oh
いっしょになれるライブ
A concert where we can be together
Gimme gimme, gimme gimme, gimme gimme high
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from any direction.
Woah-oh-oh-oh, Woah-oh-oh-oh
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。
I'm right here.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper Jumpin' now!
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From watching a concert, to meeting at one.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to Participate in Nepolabo Live
聖なる夜
A holy night.
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When the four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ！
Now!
Hyper Jumpin’ 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's jump over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで 飛ばして行け
Get high, until we turn to ash, keep on going!
Hyper Jumpin’ 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin'! Even beyond the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer.
Oh... みるだけじゃない
Oh... It's not just for watching.
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can be together.
360度 どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
Oh... もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
Oh... I want to jump higher and higher.
Hyper Jumpin’ Now!
ここにある。手が触れそうなほど。
It's right here. So close you could touch it.
Hyper Jumpin’ Now!
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you meet.
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Now!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap across!
ハイになって ハイになるまで ダンスしていたい
Getting high, I want to keep dancing until I'm high!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even across the ocean!
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer!
みるだけじゃない
More than just watching.
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly even higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
I'm right here. Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' now!
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you meet.
ねぽらぼライブ 参加方法
How to Join the NePoLaBo Live
ホロアースからの参加
IDカードホルダーを購入してライブ会場に入場
Joining via Holoearth:
Purchase an ID card holder to enter the venue
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Performance Schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
NePoLaBo Support Set
デジタルグッズ (ホロアースのアイテム)
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
NePoLaBo Live Commemorative T-Shirt
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
NePoLaBo Live Photo Contest
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Now!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap across!
ハイになって ハイになるまで ダンスしていたい
Getting high, I want to keep dancing until I'm high!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even across the ocean!
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer!
みるだけじゃない
More than just watching.
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly even higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
I'm right here. Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' now!
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you meet.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
NepoLabo Live Participation Method
ホロアースからの参加
IDカードホルダーを購入してライブ会場に入場
Participate via Holoearth
Purchase an ID card holder to enter the live venue
聖なる夜
Holy Night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When the four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap over
派手になって派手になるまで 楽し劇的な
Let's get flashy, until it's dazzling, fun and dramatic
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', all the way across the sea
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just for watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ここにいる。
We are here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
2025.12.21 Sun
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you meet.
皆様、メリークリスマス！
Everyone, Merry Christmas!
本日はねぽらぼライブ re:VISIONにご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for joining us today for NepoLabo Live re:VISION.
ライブ開始はこの後19時からの予定となっていますので、今しばらくお待ちください。
The live performance is scheduled to start at 7:00 PM, so please wait just a bit longer.
本公演のチラ見せ部分は、動画のYouTubeへの投稿が可能です。
You are allowed to post the "sneak peek" portions of this performance as videos on YouTube.
が、しかし、他のSNSは音声なしの30秒以内の動画の投稿をお願いします。
However, for other social media, please limit video posts to under 30 seconds and without audio.
静止画のスクリーンショットや感想などは、全編を通じて可能なので、いっぱい呟きお願いします！
Screenshots and your thoughts can be shared throughout the entire event, so please tweet lots!
はい！
Alright!
禁止事項ですが、本公演のミラー配信、並びに音声ありのライブ本編動画のSNSへの投稿となっています。
As for prohibited acts: mirror streaming of this performance and posting the main live footage with audio on social media.
音声なしでも30秒を超える動画のSNS投稿も禁止となっています。
Posting videos longer than 30 seconds on social media is also prohibited, even without audio.
ルールを正しく守ってライブを楽しんでください。
Please follow the rules and enjoy the live show!
さあ、みんな、遊びに来る準備はできてるかな？
So, is everyone ready to come and play?
ねねが描いたＴシャツ着てる人いるかな？
Is anyone wearing the T-shirt I designed?
雪民さんたちがどんな姿で会いに来てくれるか楽しみ！
I'm excited to see what everyone looks like!
ホロアースのライブだから、好きな服装でライブ見れるのもいいよね！
Since it's Holoearth, you can wear whatever you like!
スクショも撮っていいみたいなので、いろんな角度からたくさん撮ってほしいです！
You can also take screenshots, so please take lots from various angles!
そう、普通のライブだと動いて見て回ったりはできないもんね。
Right, you can't usually walk around and explore in a normal concert.
ねねたちの最高の写真、期待してるぞー！
We're looking forward to seeing your best photos of us!
というわけで、ライブ開始まで、もうしばらくお待ちください。
With that said, please wait a little longer for the concert to start.
一緒にライブ、盛り上がっていこー！
Let's get hyped for the concert together!
おー！
Yeah!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION 始まるぞー！
Nepolabo Live re:VISION is starting!
ちょっと早めのクリスマス、盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's get hyped for an early Christmas!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そう もっともっと
鮮やかに輝いて ハート急展開 ピュア
Hyper Jumpin' let's jump out, more and more
shine brilliantly, heart's sudden change, pure
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先までは もっと もっと
刺激がほしいの
Hyper Jumpin' to the end of the dream,
I want more and more excitement
ハイ！ みんなジャンプして！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hi! Everyone jump! Hi! Hi! Hi!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ハイ！ 行くぜ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hi! Let's go! Hi! Hi! Hi!
Hyper Jumpin'!
子供じゃない ハシャぐ方がお得でしょ
I'm not a child, but it's better to have fun, right?
ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！
Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!
計算外 カラー変えていけるでしょ
Calculation error, we can change colors, right?
ポルカ！ポルカ！ポルカ！
Polka! Polka! Polka!
意外な子 もう打ち返し まっくるメンション
Unexpected girl, already returning the mention
ラミィ！ラミィ！ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
カットオフ 乗りこなして進むミッション
Cut off, mastering the mission as we go
ぼたん！ぼたん！ぼたん！
Botan! Botan! Botan!
このまま スピード加速して
さとりつく先に 何があるんだろう
Speeding up just like this,
I wonder what lies at the destination
止まらない 気持ちは加速つけて 次元を超えて行こう
I can't stop, my feelings are accelerating,
let's cross dimensions
行くぞー！ さあ！
Let's go! Here we go!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
輪になってハイになって まるで星屑キラ
Hyper Jumpin' let's bounce,
in a circle, getting high, like stardust glitter
Hyper Jumpin' ドアの向こうまで
もっともっと 近づきたいの
Hyper Jumpin' beyond the door,
I want to get closer and closer
Woo oh oh Woo oh oh
ドキドキしたい キミ・キミ・キミ ハイ！
I want my heart to throb for you, you, you! Hi!
Woo oh oh Woo oh oh もっともっと 高く飛びたいの
Woo oh oh Woo oh oh
I want to fly higher and higher
ハイ！ ハイ！ 360度 楽しめてるかー！？ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Are you enjoying the 360 view!? Hi! Hi!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ハイ！ みんな！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hi! Everyone! Hi! Hi! Hi!
Hyper Jumpin'!
ナナメから 攻めていけ 続くクエスト
Attacking from an angle, the quest continues
ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！
Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!
ネガティブを 切り裂いてくれるセンサー
A sensor that cuts through negativity
ポルカ！ポルカ！ポルカ！
Polka! Polka! Polka!
溢れ出す コメントと駆け引きセッション
An overflowing session of comments and bargaining
ラミィ！ラミィ！ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
エイムを 鍛えて狙い撃つフィクション
Training my aim to shoot through the fiction
準備はー？ 撃てー！
Ready? Fire!
It's one na na 好きになる ma ma ma
邪魔するノイズは 撃ち消して パンパンパン！
Shoot down the distracting noise, bang bang bang!
ジャンピング 期待だけ 味わい尽くして
笑い飛ばして かき回せ 行きじゃパラレパナ！
Jumping, enjoy the expectations to the fullest,
laugh it off, stir it up, let's go parallel!
このまま 僕ら旅をして
たどり着く先に 何があるんだろう
Traveling just like this,
I wonder what lies at the destination
信じた 未来とリンクして 次元を超えて行こう さあ！
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Linking with the future we believed in,
let's cross dimensions, come on! Hyper Jumpin' let's jump over!
ハイに鳴って ハイに鳴るまで
Until it gets loud, until it becomes high
もっと新世代な ハイパージャンピン
A more next-gen Hyper Jumpin'
ハイパージャンピン
Hyper Jumpin'
見るも向こうまでも もっと もっと
To where you see and beyond, more and more
近づきたいの
I want to get closer
Wow Wow ドキドキしたい
Wow Wow, I want to feel my heart pounding
キニキニしあいたい
I want to care about you
Wow Wow もっと もっと
Wow Wow, more and more
高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイパージャンピン
High! High! High! High! High! High! Hyper Jumpin'
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ねぽらぼライブ re：VISION Holoearth Live
NePoLaBo Live re:VISION Holoearth Live
イエーイ！ 始まったー！ イエーイ！
Yay! It's started! Yay!
すごーい！
Amazing!
みんな元気？ ねぽらぼだよー！
How's everyone doing? It's NePoLaBo!
というわけで、自己紹介いきましょう！
So, let's go around with self-introductions!
ねねねね、ねねからだー！
Nene-ne-ne, I'll start!
じゃあみんな、アイテムとかの準備いいですかー？
So everyone, are you ready with your items and things?
順番にいっきますからね、みんなアイテムの準備してくださいね
We'll go in order, so everyone please get your items ready
「ねぽらぼ」で行くからね、準備するね
We'll go by 'Ne-Po-La-Bo', so get ready
どれくらいいます？ この準備
How much time is left? For this prep
ちょっと待ったほうがいいか？
Should we wait a bit?
ちょっと待って、みんなアイテムのショートカットにペンライト入れといてね
Wait a bit, everyone put your penlights in the item shortcut
1, 2, 3, 4で、こう取り出してね
Take them out like this with 1, 2, 3, and 4
よっしゃ、5, 4, 3, 2, 1, はいどうぞ！
Alright, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, here you go!
1, 2, 3, はい！
1, 2, 3, go!
じゃあみんな行くよ、こんねねー！
Okay everyone, here we go, Kon-Nene!
ホロライブ5期生、ねぽらぼの「ね」、みんなの心の... せーの！
Hololive 5th gen, the 'Ne' of NePoLaBo, everyone's heart's... ready, set!
エナジードリンク！
Energy Drink!
ハッピー桃鈴ねねです、よろしくね！ よろしくお願いします！
I'm the happy Momosuzu Nene, nice to meet you! Looking forward to it!
hololive 5th Generation
じゃあ次、はい、切り替えて、切り替えて！
Next, okay, switch it up, switch!
コンポル、尾丸ポルカだよー！
Kon-Pol, it's Omaru Polka!
いつものいくか、ポルカおるかー？
Shall we do the usual? Is Polka here?
おるよー！ はい、ねぽらぼの「ぽ」、尾丸ポルカです！
She's here! Yes, the 'Po' of NePoLaBo, I'm Omaru Polka!
よろしく！
Nice to meet you!
こんらみー！
Kon-Lamy!
ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです！ ラミィちゃんしかー？
I'm Yukihana Lamy of Hololive 5th gen! Only Lamy-chan...?
愛せんらみー！ ラミィだよ！ 雪花ラミィだよ！
Can love Lamy! It's Lamy! I'm Yukihana Lamy!
自画自賛！
Self-praise!
はい、そして、最後、最後、みんな準備してるー？
Yes, and then, the last, the last, is everyone ready?
準備してる？ 何の準備？ 準備してる？ 何の準備？
Are you ready? Ready for what? Are you ready? Ready for what?
準備してるよ、お散歩お散歩
I'm ready, walking, walking
なんかステップあるじゃん、ララライ！
There are some steps, aren't there? La-La-Lai!
ホロライブ5期生、獅白ぼたんです！ よろしくお願いします！
Hololive 5th gen, I'm Shishiro Botan! Nice to meet you!
イエーイ！ 料理いただきます！ いただきますよー！
Yay! I'll have the food! I'm eating!
はい、皆さんにバッチリ決まったところで、新しい試み、リビジョンライブということで
Yes, now that we've all decided, this is a new attempt, the Re:VISION Live
詳しいことは概要欄やホロアースの公式ホームページを確認してください
For details, please check the description box or the official Holoearth website
はい、ということで、今日はでもみんながアバターで参加してるし
Yes, so, since everyone is participating as avatars today
いろんな角度からのこの振り付け、確認してほしいなと思います
I'd like you to check out this choreography from various angles
ねねの服着ている人はいると信じてるからね、みんな！
I believe there are people wearing Nene's outfit, everyone!
いるよー！ みんなもっとよく見せて、いいよいいよ、いいよ、いいよ
They're here! Everyone show me more, good, good, good, good
お、いいよ、こっちが写真撮るんだね、ね、みんなとやれることなんかない？ おまる
Oh, good, I'll take a photo, hey, is there anything we can do with everyone? Omaru
え、何かな、何でしょうね、よし、あれやろうあれ、みんなで走りましょう、皆さん
Eh, what could it be? Let's do that, let's all run, everyone
走るよ！ ポルカから走るよ、ここから
Let's run! I'll start running, from here
ポルカが先頭で、大きくぐるっと走ってみよう
Polka will take the lead, let's try running in a big circle
オッケー、じゃあみんな集合集合、みんなついてきてね
Okay, everyone gather up, follow me
じゃあせーので行くか、はい、じゃあせーの、うわー！
Shall we go on 'ready, set, go'? Okay, ready, set, go! Whoa!
全然早い奴がいます、早いやつがいる、早い早い
There's someone totally fast, someone's fast, fast, fast
アハハハ、早い早い、はい、はいはいはい、はいはいはい、はいはいはい
Ahahaha, fast, fast, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
早くしてください、ぼたんさんが走ってます
Please hurry, Botan-san is running
ラミィちゃんついてこれないよ、大丈夫？
Lamy-chan can't keep up, are you okay?
あ、反対回り行きます！ 本気だ！ 全然本気の奴がいる
Oh, going the other way! She's serious! There's someone totally serious
大丈夫か？ はい、本気の奴がいます、早い早い
Are you okay? Yes, there's a serious one, fast, fast
反対周りですこっち、ありり？ 出遅れてる？ 逆に
The other way, this way, wait? Am I lagging? On the contrary
リビジョン！ お疲れ様ー！
Re:VISION! Good work everyone!
はい、みんなお疲れ様ー、みんなと走れて楽しい！
Yes, good work everyone, it's fun to run with everyone!
じゃあ一緒に走れることなかなかないからね、あ、ちなみにですね
It's not often we get to run together like this, oh, by the way
本番の曲の最中ですが、周りの人がね、まあ、ジャンプするとか
During the actual song performance, people around you, well, if they jump
も見え... 見えやすいように、配慮してください、ジャンプ、ピピ！
To make it... easier to see, please be considerate, jump, PiPi!
前寄りの人に配慮して、配慮して、配慮して
Be considerate of the people in front, be considerate, be considerate
はい、盛り上がってるところ申し訳ないんですが
Yes, I'm sorry to interrupt while you're all so hyped up
ここで悲しいお知らせがあります
But I have some sad news to share here
えー！ 何何？ ということで皆さんすみません
Eh! What is it? So, everyone, sorry
YouTubeとホロアースのエントランスであるボーカルスクエアでの無料配信はここまでとなっております
The free broadcast on YouTube and at the Vokal Square entrance of Holoearth ends here
ねぽらぼライブ re：VISION Holoearth Live
NePoLaBo Live re:VISION Holoearth Live
うわー！
Whoa!
はい、すみません。
Yes, sorry.
引き続き、ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION
Next, the main part of Nepolabo Live re:VISION
ホロアースライブ、本編が配信されますので、
Holoearth Live will be streamed,
YouTubeで見てる方は動画の概要欄をチェックしてください！
so those watching on YouTube, please check the video description!
はーい！
Okay!
で、チケット持っている方で、
And for those who have tickets,
まだこっちに来てない、Focal Squareのみんなは、
everyone in the Focal Square who hasn't come here yet,
よかったらこっちに来てください。
please come over if you'd like.
来てください。
Please come.
じゃあ、というわけで、はい。
Well then, here we go.
YouTubeのみんな、バイバーイ！
Everyone on YouTube, bye-bye!
さわやかだな。
That was refreshing.
というわけで、次からはソロ曲ですが、
So, solo songs are up next,
まずは誰からかなー？
but who's first?
誰かなー？
I wonder who?
誰かな、誰かな、誰かなー？
Who could it be? Who could it be?
もっと！もっと！
More! More!
ねねちゃーん！
Nene-chan!
はーい！ねねちゃん！
Yes! Nene-chan!
それではよろしく！
Please enjoy!
みんな、どんどん盛り上がって行こうぜー！
Everyone, let's keep getting hyped!
オー！
Yeah!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.